<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Let\'s Go</string>
    <string name="YOUR_API_KEY">AIzaSyCoLVhPaScRBacmyuwXnguN56LQhFDxjr0</string>

<string name="text1">Per day cost for per room :10,000 Taka only.Free Wi-fi,pool,restaurant,car parking facility available.Furnished with hifh class furniture.Beautiful view from veranda.
  </string>
    <string name="text2">Per day cost for per room :15,000 Taka only.Room is very nice and cosy.Complementary airport pickup provided.Swimmimg pool,indoor and outdoor playground for kids</string>
    <string name="text3">Per day cost for per room :5,000 Taka only.Featuring free WiFi, buffet breakfast, fitness center and an indoor swimming pool.The hotel has a barbecue and spa center, and guests can enjoy a meal at the restaurant. Free private parking is available on site. </string>

    <string name="text4">Per day cost for per room :11,000 Taka onlyLuxury hotel in Dhaka with outdoor pool, restaurant.Car renting service available.</string>

    <string name="text5">Per day cost for per room :5,000 Taka only.Luxury hotel with well decorated furniture.Large room,pool.</string>
    <string name="text6">Per day cost for per room :9,000 Taka only.Conveniences include desks and complimentary newspapers, and housekeeping is provided daily.Has valet parking.</string>

    <string name="text7">Per day cost for per room :5,000 Taka only.Sophisticated, high-end brand with innovative lobbies, guestrooms, and public spaces.Full-service restaurant and room service.</string>
    <string name="text8">Per day cost for per room :4,000 Taka only.Features a fitness center and a terrace. Offering a restaurant, the property also has a bar.</string>

    <string name="text9">Per day cost for per room :7,000 Taka only.Tiger Garden Int Hotel is located in Khulna and features free bikes and fitness center. This 3-star hotel offers a 24-hour front desk, an ATM and free WiFi. The restaurant serves Asian cuisine.All rooms are equipped with a terrace.</string>
    <string name="text10">Per day cost for per room :4,000 Taka only.The resort is located in the Rangpur of Bangladesh in the midst of a very mind blowing natural beauty. Rooms and surroundings are very clean, stuffs a very polite. Breakfast, lunch, dinner everything is very well maintained. Children can enjoy indoor play ground. </string>

    <string name="text11">Per day cost for per room :9,000 Taka only.Quite eccentric place in a natural environment. Service and room quality is good. The staffs are quite friendly. </string>
    <string name="text12">Per day cost for per room :7,000 Taka only.Featured amenities include complimentary newspapers in the lobby, dry cleaning/laundry services, and luggage storage. A roundtrip airport shuttle is provided at no charge.</string>
    <string name="text13">Per day cost for per room :10,000 Taka only.With a stay at Hotel Metro International in Sylhet, you will be convenient to Shrine of Hazrat Shah Jalal and Shahi Eidgah.Satisfy your appetite at the hotels restaurant, which serves lunch and dinner. Dining is also available at a coffee shop/café, and 24-hour room service is provided.</string>
	<string name="dp1">Time:10.00a.m. to 10.00p.m. on special days, Govt. holidays and Fridays.
             \n\nRides: All rides are of international standard in Fantasy Kingdom. These rides are paddle boat, magic carpet, bumper boat, bumper cart, ezdz, zuzu train, roller coaster, happy kangaroo, shanta maria, giant flume, barely bird etc.
               \n\nRegular Ticket: 380 tk (each)</string>
    <string name="dp2">Time:10.00a.m. to 8.00p.m.Every Day
             \n\nRides: Wheel train, a merry-go-round and a number of wheel-based rides,a fighter jet
               \n\nRegular Ticket: 10 tk (each)</string>

    <string name="dp3">Time:09.00a.m. to 6.00p.m.Every Day.Wednesday Closed.
             \n\nRides: Kite flying,Bumper train,a merry-go-round ,phantom hill,#D Movie,Paddle Boat
               \n\nRegular Ticket: 400 tk (each)</string>
    <string name="dp4">Time:10.00a.m. to 5.00p.m.Every Day.Sunday Closed.
             \n\nAttaction:The zoo exhibits 58 species of mammals, including elephants, cheetahs, rhinos, zebras, waterbucks, otters, hyenas, deer, giraffes, impala, black bears, tapirs, hippos, lions, many species of monkeys, chimpanzees, baboons, and Bengal tigers.
              \n\nThe aviaries at the zoo house more than 1500 birds representing 91 species.Elephant-back and horse-back rides are available at the zoo and fishing also.[
               \n\nRegular Ticket: 20 tk (each)</string>

    <string name="dp5">Time:11.00a.m. to 5.00p.m.Every Day
             \n\nAttraction: It is a knowledge center for nature lovers and botanists and a tourist destination. The herbarium has a scientific collection of approximately 100,000 preserved specimens of plants.Bangladesh National Herbarium collection of plant and tree species is large. The garden houses about 56,000 individual trees, herbs, and shrubs including a huge collection of aquatic plants. Rare and exotic plant species in the garden include:Anthurium,
Camphor,Rabbit fern,Dambia

               \n\nRegular Ticket: 10 tk (each)</string>

    <string name="dp6">Time:08.00a.m. to 9.00p.m.Every Day.
             \n\nAttraction: Ramna Park now grows 71 species of flowering trees shrubs, perennials, and annuals, 36 species fruit bearing plant, 33 species medicinal plant and 41 species of forestry and 11 other species. Walkways inside park have been widened and five new gates built for entry from different sides. The Park features many beautiful and modern venues for relaxation.
               \n\nRegular Ticket: No entry fee.</string>

    <string name="dp7">Time:11.00a.m. to 7.00p.m.Every Day.
                 \n\nAttraction: Tomb of Pari Bibi,Lalbagh Fort Mosque,Diwan-i-Alam(a two storied residence)
                   \n\nRegular Ticket: 50 tk(each).</string>

    <string name="dp8">Time:07.00a.m. to 7.00p.m.Every Day.
                 \n\nAttraction: The enormous design includes a half-circular arrangement of columns to symbolise the mother, with her fallen sons, standing on the monument\'s central dais, and the red sun shining behind. The Central Shaheed Minar of Dhaka goes up to a height of 14 metres (46 ft) and was made with marble stones. The stairs and barrier are highlighted in white, to create a divine look. The fence on both sides is painted with lines from poems of legendary poets in iron letters.
        \n\nAs the visitors enter the monument they will find two statues of the patriots who sacrificed their lives in that heinous police firing of 1952. The marble floor was designed to reveal the moving shadows of the columns. The basement of the Shaheed Minar also included a 1,500-square-foot (140 m2) mural representing the history of the Language Movement.
                   \n\nRegular Ticket: 50 tk(each).</string>
    <string name="dp9">Time:07.00a.m. to 7.00p.m.Every Day.
                 \n\nAttraction: The palace Ahsan Manzil is divided into two parts: the eastern side and the western side.There are attractive wooden stairs in the room that is attached to the north of the domed room.
                       \n\n The verandas and rooms are covered with marble. The doorways are placed within semicircular arches. The inner doors had multi-colored glasses. Wooden beams supported the roof of these rooms. The architecture and the decoration is one of a kind in whole Bangladesh.
        \n\nRegular Ticket: 50 tk(each).</string>
    <string name="dp10">Time:07.00a.m. to 7.00p.m.Every Day.Sunday Closed.
                         \n\nAttraction: The area is huge. There are a few fun rides available. Many restaurants are available inside. Water park is avaible with additional entry tickets. Boat trip in the lake is nice. Nice place to visit with kids. Whole day can be spent there if someone is interested in water activities.
                           \n\nRegular Ticket: 100 tk(each)</string>
    <string name="dp11">Time:10.00a.m. to 10.00p.m.Every Day.Monday Closed.
             \n\nRides: Paddle boat, magic carpet, bumper boat, roller coaster, happy kangaroo, shanta maria,marry-go_-ound etc.
               \n\nRegular Ticket: 15 tk (each)</string>
    <string name="dp12">Time:10.00a.m. to 06.00p.m.Every Day.
                      \n\nAttraction: Initially there were 5 different species and total number of animals were 23. After that the total number of species has been increased to 67, among them 32 are Mammals, 28 are Birds and rest of 7 are Reptiles within the total number of animals are 367.
              \n\nRegular Ticket: 30 tk (each)
</string>
    <string name="dp13">Description: Cox\'s Bazar  is a city, fishing port, tourism centre and district headquarters in southeastern Bangladesh. The beach in Coxs Bazar is sandy and has a gentle slope; with an unbroken length of 120 km (75 mi), it is the longest natural sea beach in the world.It is a famous visiting spot in Bangladesh full of natural beauty.</string>

    <string name="dp14">Description: St. Martin\'s Island (Bengali: সেন্ট মার্টিন্স দ্বীপ) is a small island (area only 8 km2) in the northeastern part of the Bay of Bengal, about 9 km south of the tip of the Cox\'s Bazar-Teknaf peninsula, and forming the southernmost part of Bangladesh. There is a small adjoining island that is separated at high tide, called Chera Dwip.</string>

    <string name="dp15">Description: Kaptai Lake is the largest man made lake in Bangladesh.[1] It is located in the Kaptai Upazila under Rangamati District of Chittagong Division. The lake was created as a result of building the Kaptai Dam on the Karnaphuli River, as part of the Karnaphuli Hydro-electric project. The Kaptai Lake\'s average depth is 100 feet (30 m) and maximum depth is 490 feet (150 m).</string>
    <string name="dp16">Description: Inani Beach (also Enani Beach) is an 18-kilometre-long (11 mi) sea beach in Ukhia Upazila of Cox\'s Bazar District, Bangladesh. It has a lot of coral stones, which are very sharp. These coral stones look black and green, and they are found in summer or rainy seasons.</string>
    <string name="dp17">Description: Sajek Valley is an emerging tourist spot in Bangladesh situated among the hills of Kasalong range of mountains in Sajek union in Rangamati District. The valley is 1,800 feet (550 m) above sea level.
        \n\nSajek valley is known as the Queen of Hills and Roof of Rangamati.Sajek valley is famous for its natural beauty. The valley is surrounded by mountains, dense forest, grasslands hilly tracks. Many small rivers flow through the mountains among which Kachalong and Machalong are notable. On the way to Sajek valley, one has to cross the Mayni range and Mayni river. The road to Sajek has high picks and falls.
    </string>

    <string name="dp18">Description: Observe the diverse wildlife found at Himchori Waterfall, with over 55 animal species and 117 plant species located in the national park, including elephants, tigers, wild boars, sloths, and many more. A nearby waterfall cascades over moss-covered stones, while the beach looks out over the Bengal bay. Take the forest trail up the hill to enjoy panoramic sea views, or stay nearer the beach and treat yourself to a fresh coconut. Make Himchori Waterfall a centerpiece of your Cox\'s Bazar vacation itinerary,</string>
    <string name="dp19">Description: One of the best places at Bandarban, Bangladesh. The trip to nilgiri by \'Chander gari\' offers a broad view of hill way. And then the eye soothing beauty of the world you will get at the moutain top, is beyond comparison.

\n\nOver 2,700 species of flowering plants, 160 species of fern and fern allies, countless types of flowerless plants, mosses, fungi, algae, and land lichens are found in the sholas of the Nilgiris.
    No other hill station has so many exotic species.
    Much of the Nilgiris\' natural montane grasslands and shrublands interspersed with sholas has been much disturbed or destroyed by extensive tea plantations, easy motor-vehicle access, extensive commercial planting and harvesting of non-native eucalyptus and wattle plantations, and cattle grazing.</string>

    <string name="dp20">Description: Shat Gambuj mosque is a UNESCO World Heritage Site, is a mosque in Bangladesh, the largest in that country from the Sultanate period.
    The \'Sixty Dome\' Mosque has walls of unusually thick, tapered brick in the Tughlaq style and a hut-shaped roofline that anticipates later styles. The length of the mosque is 160 feet and width is 108 feet. There are 77 low domes arranged in seven rows of eleven, and one dome on each corner, bringing the total to 81 domes.
    It has been described as "the most impressive Muslim monuments in the whole of the Indian subcontinent.</string>

    <string name="dp21">Description: It is a three storied building constructed with brick, timber, corrugated tin sheets etc. The building is pyramid shaped with a terrace. The total area of the compound is 11 acres. The place is famous for Kuthi Bari; a country house made by Dwarkanath Tagore. Rabindranath Tagore lived a part of life here and created some of his memorable poems while living here</string>
    <string name="dp22">Description: Dublar Char is a beautiful island in the Sundarbans of Bangladesh. The beach is remarkably wonderful. One can enjoy the beauty of sunset. The soft breeze exuding heavenly vibes.
    Tourists can see the whole process of dry fish making procedures, life of fishermen, their fishing trawlers. There is a small market for sea fish. Various types of fishes are traded there. This market is renowned for the cheap price of dry fish.

        \n\nDublar char is also famous for seagulls. The bunch of white seagulls are catching fish from the sea and playing with the flow of sea water, this scenery is beyond to describe with words.</string>


    <string name="dp23">Description: The Sundarban forest lies in the vast delta on the Bay of Bengal formed by the super confluence of the Ganges, Hooghly, Padma, Brahmaputra and Meghna rivers across southern Bangladesh. The seasonally flooded Sundarbans freshwater swamp forests lie inland from the mangrove forests on the coastal fringe.
        The forest covers 10,000 square kilometres (3,900 sq mi) of which about 6,000 square kilometres (2,300 sq mi) are in Bangladesh.
        \n\nIt became inscribed as a UNESCO world heritage site in 1997. The Sundarbans flora is characterised by the abundance of sundari, gewa, goran and keora all of which occur prominently throughout the area.
        The region is also known to contain numerous wildlife species, birds and reptiles, including Bengal tiger, chital, crocodile, snakes many of which are considered endangered</string>


    <string name="dp24">Description: Bichnakandi is a quarry spot that is used to collect rocks from the riverbed.At present,it is one of the most visited tourist spots in Bangladesh.People from other countries visit Bangladesh for its natural beauty and this place attract them. Interesting fact is this place is alongside Bangladesh-India border and has two tectonic plates on the verge of colliding. Geologist also have proved that these kinds of places in Earth have a high rate of earthquakes. Same can be told for Jaflong, Lalakhal, the entire Manipur estate in India, San Andreas Fault etc</string>
    <string name="dp25">Description: Jaflong is one of the most attractive tourist spots in Sylhet division. It is about 60 km from Sylhet town and takes two hours drive to reach there. Jaflong is also a scenic spot nearby amidst tea gardens and rare beauty of rolling stones from hills. It is situated besides the river Mari in the lap of Hill Khashia.</string>
    <string name="dp26">Description: Ratargul Swamp Forest is a freshwater swamp forest located in Gowain River, Fatehpur Union, Gowainghat, Sylhet, Bangladesh. It is the only swamp forest located in Bangladesh and one of the few freshwater swamp forest in the world.
    Tourists mostly go to see the forest in monsoon. One needs to take permission from the forest office to visit the forest. A local boat needs to be hired to travel through the swamp forest</string>

    <string name="dp27">Description: Shajalal mazar is a religious places of Bangladesh.It is a beautiful tourist attraction for its design.. Many pilgrims are gathered that place to see his grave(Mazar) for praying. </string>
    <string name="dp28">Description: The Keane Bridge is popularly known as Surma Bridge as it’s over the Surma River,
        a notable landmark of Sylhet and called the gateway to Sylhet city. According to the history, the bridge was built in 1936 during British reign and is named after Sir Michael Keane, who was the English Governor of Assam during that time.
        \n\nIt is an old iron bridge but still being used mostly by the pedestrians and rickshaws. It’s worth to roaming around the bridge during late afternoon and a walk over it to see the Surma River. There is a Floating restaurant called Surma Cruise, which is a good place to have dinner.</string>
    <string name="dp29">Description:Sreemangal is known as the tea capital of Bangladesh. It covers an overall are of 450 sq. km. The opulent green tea plantation attracts most tourists. It has overall 163 tea plantations. The tea of highest quality is produced here.</string>
    <string name="dp30">Description: Mahasthangarh is one of the earliest urban archaeological sites so far discovered in Bangladesh. The village Mahasthan in Shibganj thana of Bogra District contains the remains of an ancient city which was called Pundranagara or Paundravardhanapura in the territory of Pundravardhana.A limestone slab bearing six lines in Prakrit in Brahmi script, discovered in 1931.</string>
    <string name="dp31">Description: Evidence of the rise of Mahayana Buddhism in Bengal from the 7th century onwards, Somapura Mahavira, or the Great Monastery, was a renowned intellectual centre until the 12th century. Its layout perfectly adapted to its religious function, this monastery-city represents a unique artistic achievement.It is a part of world heritage.</string>
    <string name="dp32">Description: The Nagar is a branch of the Karatoya and serves as the boundary between the Shibganj and Bogra thanas, for about 11 kilometres (7 mi). It then passes between the former and the Dhupchanchia Upazila and then Adamdighi down to the village of Champapur. It then turns off west wards and passing through the Dupchanchia thana enters Rajshahi district. It falls in the Atrai, at Singra Upazila in the Natore District. It is a tortuous river,</string>

    <string name="dp33">Description: Ramsagar National Park located in Dinajpur.The Park built around a large water reservoir known as “small sea” built in the 18th century by Raja Ram Nath.The tank(biggest man made pond Bangladesh) that by the 18th century was renowned for fishing,boating and picnics,it took the name Ramsagar-the sea of Ram.</string>

</resources>

